Inscribe your answer on the rooftop over there.
I'll kill Huey Laforet.
You will surely be happy!
It's finished!
It's perfect!
Y-You know Big Brother?
That's because I was the one who dropped him.
フライ ング プツシ一フッ 卜での惨事は
なかったことに されつつあります
The tragic incidents on the Flying Pussyfoot are slowly being swept under the rug.
乗客の一部には多額の慰謝料とともに
ロ封じが行われています
Some of the passengers are being silenced with large sums of money.
金の出どころはベリアム上院議員と
ネブラ社のようで…
It seems that the source of money is from Senator Beriam and the Nebula Company.
それはつま り 今回の事件がある程度
In other words, this incident was devised to a certain extent?
仕組まれたもので
あったということかね?
恐らく
Probably.
未確認情報ですが
ベリアム上院議員が
This is unconfirmed information, but there's also talks that Senator Beriam visited Huey Laforet.
ヒユ一イラフォレッ卜と
面会したという話がありまして
ほう
ベリアム議員には
ヒユ一イラフォレッ卜に対する
Senator Beriam seems to have a rivalry with Huey Laforet for some reason.
何 らかの対抗意識があるよ うです
つまり今回の事件も
ーつの実験だつたのではないかと
In other words, I believe this incident was just an experiment.
随分 犠牲の多い実験だね
It sure was an experiment full of sacrifices.
彼らの目的は何だと思うかね?
二コラス君
What do you think his purpose was, Nicholas?
I wonder...
さあ‥
それは お二人のほうが
よくご存じなのでは?
I believe the both of you know better than I do.
ウホホン んん
Don't be cynical, Nicholas.
皮肉はやめたまえ 二コラス君
秘密を共有することは 君もまた
危険にさらされることになるのだ
To share the secret means to expose you to danger as well.
ヴイ一ノの件では
ほとほと懲りただろう?
I'm sure you've learned your lesson after the encounter with Vino.
Nicholas and Elean, as an information shop, let us focus only on doing our job.
二コラス君 工レアン君
我々は情報屋として淡々と
職務をこなすことに専念しよう
Devote yourself to gathering information.
ただひたすら情報を集めるのだ
好奇心や野次馬根性は捨てた まえ
Leave your inquistiveness and curiosity out of it.
はい
Understood.
それでは
Now then, please report the rest of the minor details regarding the Flying Pussyfoot.
フライングプッシ一フツ卜に関する
周辺情報の続きを頼む
はい 丿しツソフア三リ一の
ラツ ドヴしッソですが
Yes.
Regarding the Russo family's Ladd Russo...
取り調ベには
おとなしく応じているものの
He has been calm and cooperative during the investigation.
自身の殺人については すベて
正当防衛を主張しているとのこと
However, he insists the murders he committed were legitimately done in self-defense.
なあ あんた ヒユ一イ
ラフォレッ卜って知つてるか?
Hey, you.
Do you know about Huey Laforet?
ええ まあ有名人ですから
Yeah, he is a famous person after all.
Which prison is he going to?
あいつ どこの刑務所に入るんだ ?
ん一 まだ決まつてませんが
It hasn't been decided yet, but it should be the military prison on Alcatraz... Probably...
ア丿し力卜ラズの軍事刑務所じゃ
ないですかねえ 恐らく
へえ‥ そうか‥
Oh, really?
Thanks, pal.
ありがとよ
シ力ゴの不良少年
Chicago hoodlums, Jacuzzi Splot and the group he leads
ジヤグジ一'スプロッ卜に
率いられたグル一ブだけど
have been hired as the Genoard family's witnesses at the recommendation of the Flying Pussyfoot's head chef.
フライングブツシ一フッ 卜号
食堂車のコック長の紹介で
ジ工ノア一ド家の
使用人として雇われ
現在も三リオネア'ロウの
別邸に滞在中
They're now staying at the Millionaire Row Villa.
リ一ダ一のジヤグジ一は
いつたん快方に向かつたものの
Their leader, Jacuzzi, was supposed to be released at one point, but thanks to the trouble with Graham Specter,
グラハムスペク夕一との いざこざで
またケガが悪化し いまだ入院中
his injuries have worsened and he is still in the hospital.
イブジ工ノア一ドは
どうなったのかね
What about Eve Genoard?
それは角砂糖から
報告してもらいましょう
Let's have "Cube Sugar" report on that.
せめて兄に会わせてやるわけには
いかないですか?
Can't we at least let her meet her brother?
Since when did you have an interest in helping others?
いつから人助けが
趣味になったのかね
特に不利益があるとも思えませんが
I believe there is no particular disadvantage in doing so.
The spread of information is enough of a disadvantage.
情報の拡散は十分に不利益だよ
あの妹を生涯 兄とともに
It would be a different story if it was okay to lock her and her brother up in the laboratories for life.
実験施設に
閉じ込めてもいいと言うなら別だがね
なるほどね
ご苦労だった 角砂糖君
I see.
A job well done, "Cube Sugar".
食ベますか?
Would you like one?
結構
No, thanks.
食ベますか?
Would you like one?
Yes, please.
頂こう
Here you go.
どうぞ
角砂糖君 引き続き
イブ嬢の動向を見守ってくれたまえ
"Cube Sugar", please continue to watch over Miss Eve's actions.
Understood.
ところでレイチ工ル君はどうした ?
By the way, what happened to Rachel?
あ… れ 例のフライング~
プツシ一フツ 卜に乗つていた男の子に
Sh-She apparently went to see the boy who was on the Flying Pussyfoot.
会いに行つたらしいよ !
フツ なるほど
I see.
ああ ! あとこんな話が
Oh yeah, there's this rumor too...
レイチ工ルお姉ちやん !
Sister Rachel!
Thank you so much, Sister Rachel!
ありがとうございました
レイ チエ丿しお姉ちやん!
いいんだよ そんな…
Don't mention it.
本当に なんてお礼を
申し上げたらいいのか~
I don't know how to thank you.
It doesn't feel enough no matter how many times I thank you.
いくら感謝しても
し足りないくらいです
Really, don't mention it.
ほんとに
そんな気にしないで下さい
This is my husband, Manfred.
主人のマンフレツ ドです
Go on ahead.
先に行つていなさい
Yes.
はい…
それではレイチ工ルさん お元気で
Well then, Ms. Rachel. Please take care.
Come now, Mary.
さ メリ一
バイバイ お姉ちやん
Bye bye, Sister.
さようなら
Goodbye.
取つておいてくれたまえ
Take it.
ちよつと あんた !
Hey, you!
なるほど…
I see.
レイ チ工ル君も
イヤな思いをさせられたようだね
Looks like Rachel has been left with an unpleasant memory.
She won't need to steal a ride for a while now, I guess.
これで無賃乗車は当分しないで
済むんじゃないでしょうか
二コラス君
Nicholas, did I not tell you that Rachel has her own circumstances?
レイ チエル君にはレイ チ工ル君の
事情があると言っただろう
Sure.
レイ チ工ル君の父親が
鉄道技師だつたのは覚えているね?
You remember that Rachel's father was a railway engineer, right?
はい
Yes.
レイチ工ル君が幼い頃
When Rachel was young, a train accident occurred because of a damaged part.
ある列車で
部品の破損事故が起こり
The railway company pushed all the responsibility onto Rachel's father.
鉄道会社は その責任をすベて
レイ チ工ル君の父親に押しつけたのだ
失意のうちにあり ながら
Despite his disappointment, he did not stop loving trains.
それでも鉄道を愛することを
やめない父親の姿から
レイチ工ル君は
鉄道会社への怨念と
おん旛ん
Rachel must have inherited both his grudge and love toward trains.
鉄道への愛を
同時に受け止めたのだろう
In short, she stole a ride out of grudge and helped passengers out of love?
つまり怨念で無賃乗車をレて
愛で乗客を助けたというわけですか
That's right.
そのとお り だ
それはまた随分と複雑な…
Again, that's very complicated.
だから無賃乗車をからかうのは
やめたまえ 分かったね?
So stop teasing her for riding free.
Do you understand?
自重いたします
I will be careful.
これで切符を買えるだけちようだい
Give me enough tickets for this amount of cash.
Where to?
ど どちらまで?
Anywhere would be fine.
どこでも構わない…
今までの分だから
It's for the fare up until now.
What do you... mean?
あの‥ ー体‥
Don't ask anything!
何も聞かないで
But...
しかし…
話すと長いから
It's a long story!
Lまあ‥
さて 肝心のヴイ一ノの
その後だが…
Now then, what happened to Vino afterwards?
I don't know anything!
ゎ 私は知 り ませんよ
But, Nicholas...
しかしだね 二コラス君
もうヴイ一ノは
ゴメンですつたら!
I've had enough of Vino!
お兄ちゃん 誰?
Who are you?
What do you mean "who"?
誰って… ひどいな そりや
That's too cruel.
確かに今は着替えてるし
返り血も浴ぴてないけど…
It's true that I've changed my clothes, and I'm not covered in blood.
自分のことを殺そうとした
相手の声ぐらい
Don't you at least remember the voice of the person who tried to kill you?
{、
えっ川 見スておかないか? 普通
ああ 安心しろよ
列車も無事に着いたことだし
Relax.
Since the train arrived safely, I'll spare you the pain of being killed repeatedly.
もうお前のことを殺し続けるのは
勘弁してやるガら
Also...
それと 無賃乗車女さあ
Hey, free riding girl, I heard you bought tickets after that.
あれから切符を
ちゃんと買つたらしいな
That's a good girl.
偉いな オイ
つていうか
それが普通なんだけどな 本当は
Actually, what I really mean is that's the normal way.
切符を拝見…
Ticket, please.
うゎああああああああ つ つ つ !
うわああっ うわあああああぁつっっ !
安心しろつて言つたのに
I thought I told him to relax.
You're really... the conductor?
あんた‥ 車掌‥
Stop right there.
おっと 俺はもう車掌じやない
I'm not a conductor anymore.
まあ そこらへんを含めてだ
ちょつとメシでも食わないか?
Well, since we're here, let's go grab a bite.
いや ちようどさ
You see, I want some advice from a girl I'm acquainted with.
誰か知り合いの女に
相談したいことがあったんだ
About a girl who might marry me.
俺と結婚してくれるかもしれない
女のことでな…
どうだ? 行かないのか?
How about it?
Are you coming?
ゎあ
おお一
Go, go, go!
行け ! 行け! 行け!
行け! 行け!
結局 自分が一番
興奮してるじゃないですか
In the end, you're the most worked up over it.
Don't be so uptight, Mr. Maiza!
マイザ一さん
固いこと言わない 言わない
お一一つ
A little more.
あと ちよつとだぁ
行け 行け
Go, go, go!
おお一一つ ! 付け
Hurray!
フイ一ロ ! お前は今日から
ド三二ス卜だ!
Firo, starting today you're a dominist!
最大級のド三ナ一だね
The greatest domino!
ド三二ス卜 !
Dominist!
はつ?
Whatever's fine.
何でもいいけど ヒヤツホウ !
Yahoo!
ヒヤツホウ ! ヒヤツホウ ! ヒヤツホウ !
There's this girl I like.
そんなわけでな
好きな女がいるんだけど
どうやつて告白すれば
うまくいくと思う?
How do you think I should confess to her?
あ 別にお前のことじゃないから
安心していいぞ
It's not you, so don't worry.
何だ? 黙つてちや分からないぜ
Come on... If you don't say anything, I won't know how.
せめて名前くらい名乗つたらどう ?
How about telling me your name, at the least?
Oh, me?
ああ 俺か?
一応 つい こないだまでは
Well, I was Clare Standfeldt until recently.
クレアス夕ンフイ一丿しドって
名乗つてたんだがな
今はもうやめようかと
思つてるところだ
I'm thinking of ending that now.
だから はつきりとした名前は
まだない
So, I don't have an official name for now.
If you insist, you can call me Rail Tracer.
しいて言えば
レイ丿し卜レ一サ一つてとこかな
お前は ?
What about you?
私はレイチ工ル
I'm Rachel.
Rachel!
レイチ工ル!
What do you think, Rachel?
What kind of confession would be the best?
私はあんまり
普通の女の子じゃないから
I'm not a normal girl, so I don't know if I can give you any good advice.
うまくアドバイスできるかどうか
分からないけど
それなら心配するな
You don't have to worry about that!
That girl is even more abnormal than you.
その女は お前以上に
普通の女の子じゃないからな
とりあえず その無神経さを
どうにかするのが先決だと思うけど
First of all, I think you better fix that insensitivity of yours.
それで その好きな子ってのは
知り合いなの?
So, are you acquainted with that girl?
Y-Yeah.
あ ああ こないだの
あの列車で初めて会った
I met her for the first time on the train the other day.
その時は その場限りで
別れたんだけどさ…
We parted ways after that.
But she left a message behind.
彼女の害き置きがあってね…
何だ よく分からないけど
十分 脈ありじやない
Oh?
I don't know for sure, but it seems you have a good chance.
いや一 それがさ
Well, about that...
彼女が俺のことを
殺そうとしてるのか
Does she want to kill me? Or, does she want to meet me because she loves me?
それとも好きだから会いたいって
言つてるのか
I don't have a clue...
まず それが分からないんだ
もし彼女が俺のことを
殺そうとしてるんだとしたらだ
Even if she's trying to kill me, I don't think I'll stop loving her, but...
それがすなわち俺を愛してないって
ことにはならないと思うんだが
Even if you say you think that...
思うんだがつて言ゎれても
ほら 殺したいほど愛してるどかさ
Maybe she loves me so much that she wants to kill me.
Or maybe she loves me, but wants me dead to protect something more important.
もしくは 本当は好きだけど
もっと大事なもののために
死んでもらうつてパ夕一ンも
あり えるじやないか
まあ それはさておいて
正直さ
Well, putting that aside...
Honestly, I've been proposing to girls I liked but when I was rejected, I just moved on to the next one.
今までは好きになつたら
ブロポ一ズして
フラれたらすぐに次の女を探して
声をかけるつてことを
やつてきたんだけどさ
彼女の害き置きを見たり
白服と殺し合つてるとことか
But looking at her message, recalling the way she fought against the man in white without saying a word, that expressionless face...
一言もしゃベらない
あの無表情な顔とかを思い出すとm
The more I recall it, the more I love her.
思い出すたぴに
どんどん好きになるっていぅかな一m
Could it be that the first time I said I would help her...
もしかしたら最初に
彼女を助けるっ乙言ったのも…
今 思えば同情どかじやなくて
When I think of it now, it might not have been sympathy, but rather a destined love at first sight.
運命的な
一目惚れというやつかもしれない
あぁ… 今 初めてあなたも
人間なんだっ乙思えたよ
For the first time, I realized you're human too.
Up till now, you didn't think I was human?
今まで人間と
思つてなかつたのか?
と言いたいが 正直 俺も混乱してる
I would like to say that, but honestly I'm confused myself.
まあ 絶対成功すると
思つてるけどな
Well, I think it will definitely work out.
時間はかかるかもしれないが
きつとうまくいく
It might take some time, but it will surely go well.
If she doesn't give a damn about me, then I'll make her fall in love with me, no matter how many years it takes.
向こうが俺のことを
何とも思ってないって言うんなら
俺を好きにさせてみるまでさ
たとえ何年かかってもね
まだ その子は見つかつてないの ?
You haven't found her yet?
Well...
いや 実はな
居場所はもぅ分かつてるんだ
Actually, I already know where she is.
うつ…
情報屋の二コラスってのは
お前か?
Are you Nicholas from the information shop?
そうですが… え え え一 と
That's me.
U-Um...
俺は元 クレアス夕ンフイ一ルド
I used to be Clare Standfeldt,
元ヴイ一ノ
used to be Vino,
and used to be the conductor of the transcontinental railroad.
元 大陸横断鉄道車掌
何でもいいが 要するに
元そういうもんだつた者だ
Either way, I used to be one of them.
I heard you made use of a young girl and placed her in a lot of danger.
お前 年端もいかない
女の子を利用して
とっても危険な目に
遭わせたそうじゃないか
悪い奴だ
You're a bad person.
A-Aren't you misunderstanding something?
そ そんな
何か誤解されてるんじや…
Time for your punishment.
お仕置きだ 聞きたいことも
たつぷりあるしな
I have a lot of things to ask you too.
ギヤ一一一ツ
If you want to be saved, tell me now!
助けてほしければ言え !
Where is Chane, the girl who was on the Flying Pussyfoot?
フライングプツシ一フツ卜に
乗っていた
シヤ一ネという名前の女は
どこにいる !
言ぅ! 言う!
言いますから助けて一一つ !
I'LL TELL YOU, SO LET ME GO!
それなら確実ね
That's reliable, isn't it...
ああ あとは彼女の気持ちを
どう確かめるかだ
Yeah.
The next thing is how to find out her feelings.
手紙と一緒に
ブレゼン卜でも贈ったら?
Why don't you send her a letter with a present?
なるほど プレゼン 卜か
I see.
A present, huh?
That bastard!
あんの野郎…
Call Big Sis immediately!
すぐに霜さんを呼んでこい !
I'll go get Jacuzzi first.
俺は一足先に
ジヤグジ一の所に行つてくる!
Hyahoo!
ヒャツハア
ひゃっはあ
いや一 俺の贈つた服
着てくれたんだ…
She's wearing the dress I sent her.
まさか こんなに早く着てくれるとは
思わなかつたから…
I didn't think she would wear it so soon.
その 何だ
すごくうれしいゎけだが…
How do you say it, I'm really happy.
あの車から出てきた青い作業員は
誰だろうな?
I wonder who that worker in blue coming out of that car was?
追うベきかな?
Should I chase after them?
シヤ一ネなら放つておいても
あんな奴は倒してしまうわけだが…
Since it's Chane, she would beat the hell out of that guy without my help.
But... should I chase them just in case?
あ一一 でも…
とりあえず追うか?
I'm going!
追うゎ !
フツ!
No matter how you put it, it's obviously impossible to beat me.
俺を倒すことは どう者えても
不可能であるわけだが
ヤロ一 !
Looks like this ain't no joke.
ウソじやなさそうだな
Oh, sad. Let's talk about something very sad.
ああ… 悲しい
とても悲しい話をしよう
かたき
こんなにも憎い敵が
目の前にいるのに
Although my hateful enemy is right in front of me, I can't do anything for now!
俺はこれ以上
手を出すこともできない
だつてそうだろう? その男は…
But, isn't it so?
Because someday, Brother Ladd will be the one to kill that man!
いずれラツ ドの兄貴自身が
ぷち殺すんだからな
ご忠告 ありがたく
受け取つておくよ
I appreciate your warning.
忠告じやない 死刑宣告だ
It's not a warning. It's a death sentence!
行くぞ
Let's go.
I like you.
お前は気に入ったよ
えっ?
Feel free to use this warehouse anytime you like.
この貪庫でよかつたら いつでも使え
俺の所有物だ
It's my property.
Goodbye! See ya! When that annoying redhead isn't around, that is!
じやあな また会おうや
まいま
あの悪々しい赤毛が
いない時にでもな
In the end, is he a good guy or a bad guy?
結局… あの人って
いい人なの? 悪い人なの?
どつちでもいいじゃない
It doesn't matter anyhow.
After all, everyone's okay.
こうしてみんな無事だったんだから…
On the other hand, what's up with that guy?
つていうか あの人は何なの ?
何だか知らないけど…
いいんじゃない? ほつといて…
I don't know what happened, but isn't it okay to leave them that way?
それにシヤ一ネ 何だか少しだけ
うれしそうだしさ
Besides... Chane looks a little bit happy.
蓋篁もなしに帰つちまうのか?
Are you going home without a greeting?
Mr. Elmer!
工ルマ一さん
Hello there, Sylvie. It's been a long time.
やあ シルヴイ 久しぶり だな
You knew it was me...
よく分かり ましたね 私だつて
分かるさ
Of course I knew...
俺の記憶の中のシルヴィを
ちょろつと成長させたら
You look exactly like the image I had in mind of a mature you.
まさにこんな感じだからな…
いつ飲んだんだ?
When did you drink it?
Since time would stop for me, I thought it would be better to refine myself first.
どうせ時間が止まるなら
少しは自分を
磨いてからのほうカヾいいと思っzm
あの何年かあ と に
So, a few years after that.
シルヴイ20代バ一ジ ヨ ンだな
きれいだよ
Sylvie in her twenties version!
You're pretty.
セラ一ドは食ベられたのね
Szilard was eaten, wasn't he?
知つてたのか?
You knew?
That boy. He resembles Gerd.
あの男の子…
ちよつとグレツ 卜に似てた
シルヴイ 変な気を起こすなよ
Sylvie, don't be sad.
笑顔だ 笑顔になれ シルヴイ
Smile! Smile, Sylvie!
平気ですよ 工ルマ一さん
I'm fine, Mr. Elmer.
確かに… ここに来るまでは
It's true that I thought of becoming one with Gerd before I came here.
グレッ卜と ーつになりたいと
思っていたけれど…
あの子の笑顔を見てたら
そんな気もなくなりました
But when I saw that boy's smile, I changed my mind.
あの子の中ならグレッ 卜も
幸せなんじゃないかって
I think Gerd is happy too, if he's inside that boy.
Sylvie!
シルヴイ…
I have to go now.
私 行きますね
We just met after 200 years. Isn't this a bit too uneventful?
200年ぶりに会ったのに
あっさりしすきじゃないか?
I'm making a living by singing right now.
私 今 歌で暮ら してるんです
工ルマ一)
くおっ へえ一 すごいじやないか
Wow, that's something!
That's why we'll surely meet again at some club in some city.
だから どこかの町の
どこかのクラブで
きつとまた会えるわ
さよなら 工丿しマ一さん
Goodbye, Mr. Elmer.
ああ… またな シルヴイ
Yeah. See ya, Sylvie.
よお ! 久しぶりだな !
Yo! It's been a long time!
Even if you wear something like that, I know it's you right away.
そんな力ッコしてても
すぐ分かるぜ!
あんたの放つてる雰囲気は
独特だからな
I recognized you immediately, because you have a unique air of your own.
ありがとう
あの時の約束を守ってくれて
Thanks for keeping your promise.
ノ工丿! マ一丿
まる さァ ラとアの簾神左な
You're like the Arabian genie.
C雷簾の声丿
庭左し 願〔 !は3 フさはなく
7 フ左汝喰
However, I'll only grant you one wish, not three.
All right. I've decided, demon.
ノ工丿! マ一丿
よレ 決め宏よ 悪鱒
Would you look after Maiza?
マイサ一の面倒き
見ごやっごく力な! )ヵ
ぁC )フ 弟ヵ死ん左んだ
His brother died.
きフと もの實ごく
シヨッ夕き受けごる
He must be very shocked.
悪簾じやなく 7入の入閻どレ ご
Help him, not as a demon, but as a human.
あ‥っのそばZご‥ご
勇クと手伝っごやっごく力よ
Until he is able to laugh out loud.
あ! 'つヵZ 'っヵ 丈声き上げご
ダラダラと芙えるようノごなるま覆
きっとあん盧も
笑っごく力るだろ?
You'll surely laugh too.
Are you saying you want to see me laugh?
る讀簾の声丿
蒼カヾ芙うところき
見庭蝿と言5のか
ノ工丿! マ一丿
も ちろんだ ノ
Of course!
あん庭の芙顔は
きっと俺ノごヵきく力る…
Your smile will surely give me strength.
What an unbelievable guy...
C雷簾の声丿
あきれ庭男左髏
まあ ‥‥ 努ヵはレよラ
Well, fine. I shall do my best.
I would like to see your smile before I disappear,
ここはひとつ あんたの笑った顔を
見てから いなくなりたいところだが
but there are still a lot of people I have to entertain.
俺にはまだ笑わせてやんなきゃ
ならない奴が いつぱい いるんだ
200年 生きてきたけどな
たぷん人生なんて意味はない
I've lived for 200 years, but life probably has no meaning whatsoever.
だったらいっそ 苦しみだの
憎しみだのからは解放されて
So isn't it better for everyone to be free from pain and hatred, and be happy and smile?
みんな笑顔で楽しくいられたほうが
良くないか?
うつ… ゴホゴホゴホ…
See ya, demon!
じやあな 悪魔
これからもマイザ一を頼むぜ
Please take care of Maiza from now on too.
約束を守つたというより
I was really just interested, instead of keeping the promise.
俺はただ
興味深かつただけなんだがな…
まあ いい
Oh, well.
コホツ
しかし 一方的な男だ
He sure is a selfish man.
副社長
Vice President.
何だい キヤ口ル
What is it, Carol?
Where did this story begin and when does it end, anyway?
結局 このお話の始まりはどこで
終わりはいつなんですか?
ん~ 愚問だな キャロル
ひよつとして
What a silly question, Carol.
Are you by any chance still searching for the main character of this tale?
お前はまだ この物語の
主人公を探しているのではないか?
はい
Yes.
Carol, liberate yourself from the illusion.
キヤ口ル 幻想から解放されるのだ
物語に始まりがあり
終わりがあるという幻想を捨てるのだ
Put aside the illusion that there is a beginning and an ending to a tale.
物語には始まりなどない
終わりもない
There is no beginning nor ending to any given tale.
The only thing that exists is the way people relate, interact and affect each other, and how that expands throughout the world.
あるのは ただ人と人がつながり
作用し合い 影響し
拡散していく
謹のありようだけなのだ
物語に終わりなど
あっては ならないのだよ キヤロル
There should never be an ending to a tale, Carol.
Vice President, it's too hard for me.
副社長 私には難しすきます
お一 これは悪かつた
This I understand well, but sometimes all you can say is, "Oh, I see".
だカヾ そうとしか
言いようのないことも あるのだよ
じやあ 副社長 どうして物語には
終わりがあっては いけないんですか?
So, Vice President, why shouldn't there be an ending to a tale?
なぜだと思う ? キヤ 口ル
What do you think, Carol?
続きがある可能性を残したほうが
人を壽きつけられるから
Because it is easier to attract attention by leaving a possible sequel.
3 点
Three points!
それつて点数 低すきじやあ…
Isn't that too few points?
I can make infinite answers for this question.
この質問には無数の答えが
用意できるだろう
だ力ヾ お前のために あえて
分かりやすい答えを教えるとすればだ
But to make it simple for you...
はい
All right.
Because it's fun.
楽しいからだな
楽しいから?
Fun?
Yes, because it's fun.
そうだ 楽しいからだ
Wouldn't there be people who would be dissatisfied because there is no ending to the tale?
物語に終わりがないことに
不満を持つ人もいるんじゃないですか?
That is also something to look forward to, Carol.
それもまた楽しみなのだ キヤロル
3うん‥
ひつ‥
キヤロル… 目を背けるな
Carol, do not look away.
でも副社長
But, Vice President...
Do you remember that rat?
あのネズ三に見覚えはないか?
あのネズ三 今の今までどこで
とうやつて過ごしてきたのだと思う?
Until now, where and how do you think that rat has lived?
And what kind of experience would it have from now on?
そしてこれから
どのような経験をしていくのだと思う?
想像してみろ キヤ口ル イマジン
Try and imagine it, Carol. Imagine!
工へッ 副社長
私 楽しくなってきました
Vice President, I'm having a lot of fun now!
That's exactly what I mean, Carol.
そういうことだよ キヤロル
Hey, if it's fine with you, let's start out as friends.
なあ もしよかつだら…
友達からでいい
Would you fall in love with me?
俺を好きになつてくれないか?
フツ へへツ
へへ一
フンツ
ヒヤツホ一!
く一-
待て~! コラ一ツ !
Freeze!
止まれ~ !
メり一イクりスマ一ス !
Merry Christmas!
That's too early!
早い早い ーか月 早いよお !
Merry Christmas!
これだけ使やあ
This makes up for at least fifty robberies!
せめて50回分くらいの
強盗はチャラだよな!
Since we gave it to everybody, Mr. Genoard who is in Heaven is surely jumping for joy!
天国のジェノア一ドさんも
きつと喜んでるよ!
そうだな ! 遺産争いもなくなつて
That's right! All that fighting will end, and Eve and her brother will surely be happy!
イブもイブのお兄さんも
きつと幸せになってるよな!
Everyone is happy!
みんな幸せだね !
ハハ さ一て
どこに逃けるよ? 三リア
Now then, where should we run off to, Miria?!
To the ends of the universe!
どこまでも !
おっ ! 力リフォル二アで金でも掘るか
Let's go and dig gold in California!
ゴ一ル ドラツ シユだね !
It's a gold rush!
この地球から たんまり金を
かっぱらつちまおうぜ !
Let's steal all the gold from Mother Earth!
すつごお~い!
Amazing!
dokomade mo tsuzuiteru hoshizora miagete utau
I sing, looking up into the endless starry night.
kagiriaru bokutachi no eien wo yume miru melody
A melody in a dream... about our limited eternity.
mune ni afureru itoshisa no mizu wa
This water of love, overflowing from my chest...
mirai no hate de dareka ni todoku darou
I wonder if it will reach someone in the future?
shinjite iruyo
I will believe in you.
harukana toki wo kake nukete
Transcending generations of time...
bokutachi no yobigoe wa itsuka ookina uta ni naru
Will our calls turn into a beautiful song one day?
ai wo tsumuide yukeru yo
You can start building your love,
ima wa mada konnani chiisana hikari dakedo
Though right now, the light is still faint.